{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of C++ with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is C++?",
      "answers": ["Lang", "Script", "Markup"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'int'?",
      "answers": ["Number", "String", "Char"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'cout'?",
      "answers": ["Output", "Input", "Error"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'cin'?",
      "answers": ["Input", "Output", "Error"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'class'?",
      "answers": ["OOP", "Func", "Var"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'include'?",
      "answers": ["Header", "Footer", "Body"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'void'?",
      "answers": ["No ret", "Return", "Null"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'main'?",
      "answers": ["Entry", "Exit", "Loop"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'new'?",
      "answers": ["Alloc", "Delete", "Copy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'delete'?",
      "answers": ["Free", "Alloc", "Copy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
